{
    "Subj_Name":"日本人",
    "Quiz_Details":"Algorithms",
    "Quiz_No":"Quiz 4",
    "Quiz_Questions":[
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of あ",
            "answer":["あ is A","A"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of い",
            "answer":["い is I","I"]
        },{
            "question":"Equivalent of う",
            "answer":["う is U","U"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of え",
            "answer":["え is E","E"]
        },{
            "question":"Equivalent of お",
            "answer":["お is O","O"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of か",
            "answer":["か is KA","KA"]
        },{
            "question":"Equivalent of き",
            "answer":["き is KI","KI"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of く",
            "answer":["く is KU","KU"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of け",
            "answer":["け is KE","KE"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of こ",
            "answer":["こ is KO","KO"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of さ",
            "answer":["さ is SA","SA"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of し",
            "answer":["し is SHI","SHI"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of ",
            "answer":["す is SU","SU"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of せ",
            "answer":["せ is SE","SE"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of そ",
            "answer":["そ is SO","SO"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of た",
            "answer":["た is TA","TA"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of ち",
            "answer":["ち is CHI","CHI"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of つ",
            "answer":["つ is TSU","TSU"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of て",
            "answer":["て is TE","TE"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of と",
            "answer":["と is TO","TO"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of な",
            "answer":["な is NA","NA"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of に",
            "answer":["に is NI","NI"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of ぬ",
            "answer":["ぬ is NU","NU"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of ね",
            "answer":["ね is NE","NE"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of の",
            "answer":["の is NO","NO"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of は",
            "answer":["は is HA","HA"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of ひ",
            "answer":["ひ is HI","HI"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of ふ",
            "answer":["ふ is HU/FU","HU","FU"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of へ",
            "answer":["へ is HE","HE"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of ほ",
            "answer":["ほ is HO","HO"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of ま",
            "answer":["ま is MA","MA"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of み",
            "answer":["み is MI","MI"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of む",
            "answer":["む is MU","MU"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of め",
            "answer":["め is ME","ME"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of も",
            "answer":["も is MO","MO"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of や",
            "answer":["や is YA","YA"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of ゆ",
            "answer":["ゆ is YU","YU"]
        },
        {
            "question":"Equivalent of よ",
            "answer":["よ is YO","YO"]
        }
    ]
}